SpaghettiMapper — leave a map, not more spaghetti
First run — create your architect account
Home — your architecture projects
Graph lens — systems and streams
Main — the shared map
Mine — your private workspace
Inspector — dig into a system
Strand dig-in — every stream on the edge
Expand — one curve per stream
Bundle — collapse parallel streams
Clusters — name an estate on the map
Filter — dim what doesn't match
Filter — hide unmatched
Clear filters — full landscape again
Flow — Order to warehouse, full canvas
Combine — promote Mine into Main
Main after Combine
Matrix — who talks to whom
Analysis — coverage and unjustified motion
History — versions you can restore
Export — SVG, JSON, or integration register
Map the tangle. Justify the motion.